<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project parts on Martha Lucia Borras Guevara, Vladimir Finkelshtein, Sandro Mignuzzi and Anzhela Shestakova</title>
    <link>https://github.com/TuchisAnalyst/Crane-Data-Science-Project/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project parts on Martha Lucia Borras Guevara, Vladimir Finkelshtein, Sandro Mignuzzi and Anzhela Shestakova</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://github.com/TuchisAnalyst/Crane-Data-Science-Project/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Part 1: Preparing and cleaning of the data</title>
      <link>https://github.com/TuchisAnalyst/Crane-Data-Science-Project/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/TuchisAnalyst/Crane-Data-Science-Project/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Preparing a dataset will usually require some manipulation and adaptation before any kind of analyses con be performed, especially if you need to aggregate other sources of data for the analysis.
 Step 1: Data Preparation - Began with finding the right data from different sources provided by the company. Step 2: Discovering ans assesment - This step was about getting to know the data and understanding what had to be done before any analyses were done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 2: Development of the recommendation engine</title>
      <link>https://github.com/TuchisAnalyst/Crane-Data-Science-Project/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/TuchisAnalyst/Crane-Data-Science-Project/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>An implicit recommendation system was used to increase market share growth for Crane. This system is a subclass of information filtering strategy that seeks to predict a contractor&amp;rsquo;s preferences for a given product. Higher preference predictons will result in a recommendation.
  Step 1: Data Preparation - Began with finding the right data from different sources provided by the company.
  Step 2: Discovering ans assesment - This step was about getting to know the data and understanding what had to be done before any analyses were done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 3: Recommendation engine integration with Qlikview</title>
      <link>https://github.com/TuchisAnalyst/Crane-Data-Science-Project/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/TuchisAnalyst/Crane-Data-Science-Project/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>A major part of this project&amp;rsquo;s scope was to integrate our python code and models into the existing Crane BS analytics environment, which is hosted on the analytics platform QlikView. You can find a step by step guide here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
